<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nomads on Lawrence Aiello&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/nomad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nomads on Lawrence Aiello&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 07:56:50 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/nomad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomad: Colombia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/nomad/colombia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 07:56:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/nomad/colombia/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;digital-nomad-in-colombia&#34;&gt;Digital Nomad in Colombia&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve never met a person that really enjoys the Northeastern winters, we just deal with it. The past few winters, I have been traveling to warmer climates during a portion of it to get a break from the cold weather. I imagine at some point in my future, I will eventually be spending most of winter in another place. So this issue of &amp;ldquo;Digital Nomad&amp;rdquo; will be concerning my brief time spent in Latin America, specifically Colombia. I will briefly go over the two cities I visited and worked from, and at the end give some pros/cons if you are considering a trip like this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomad: China</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/nomad/china/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 16:25:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/nomad/china/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;digital-nomad-in-china&#34;&gt;Digital Nomad in China&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, I had the opportunity to travel in China. It was a month long trip and was a mixture of pleasure (sightseeing) and personal (my partner&amp;rsquo;s family is from there). Given that I recently joined my company and due to the length of the trip, I did not have the luxury of taking too much time off. I love a challenge, so I decided to work west coast US hours from Asia. Yes, you read that right. For a month straight, I worked from 12am - 8am every weekday. In this article, I want to share a little of what I saw there, and also offer some tips if you want to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
